http://www.mdcomplete.com/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS EFFECTIVE AS OF JANUARY 1, 2020.
You linked to this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") via a product website owned by MD Professional LLC ("Company"). By using the Website, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This policy applies to all online communication with the Website. When you provide us with online information through the Website, we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Please note that your visit to our Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
We only collect personally identifiable information about you via our Website when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service, or information. You may browse our Website without providing any personal information; however if, for example, you decide to place an order, we will ask you for your name, delivery and billing address, phone number, email address, credit card number and its expiration date. If you choose to complete a user registration form, survey or sweepstakes entry form, we may ask you for information such as your contact information (e.g., name, e-mail address and mailing address), age, or birth date. Occasionally, we may also ask you for other information such as gender, income level, and information about your prior experiences with the Company's products. When you submit your personally identifiable information on the Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
We may also collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular, your IP address, browser, city, time zone, referring URL, and operating system. Information gathered may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics, developing marketing plans, customizing content, and improving the Website. We may share or transfer such aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.
Our Website is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com if they want this information deleted from our files so that it is not in retrievable form. If we otherwise obtain knowledge that we have personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in our files, we will delete that information from our existing files so that it is not retrievable.
USE/DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
The Company and its affiliates and subsidiaries may use the information that you provide to fulfill your request for a product, information, or other service, or respond to an email or other request, as well as to create and deliver to you our newsletters or surveys, communications containing product information, usage tips or promotions, help improve our website(s) or services, or customize visitors' experience at our Website. The Company may also make your name, email address, mailing address and/or telephone number available to carefully selected business partners, vendors and other third party organizations to provide you with information about products, services and special offers we think may interest you or to improve our products, services and advertising. Many of our users find this a valuable and time-saving service.
We want to communicate with you via email correspondence only if you want to hear from us. If for any reason you would no longer like to receive email messages from the Company, you can email us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com to remove yourself. In addition, if you do not want us to share your personal information with third party organizations, you can email us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com to remove yourself. Please allow up to 10 days for us to process your request.
Please note, if you opt not to receive marketing emails from the Company, you may still receive "Transactional" email messages regarding your order (i.e. order confirmation, shipping information, customer service notifications, etc.) If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com.
We may contract with companies or individuals to provide certain services including email and hosting services, credit card processing, shipping, data management, surveys and marketing, promotional services, to assist in preventing or deterring fraud, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We may share personally identifiable information with Service Providers solely as appropriate for them to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose. We do not share your credit card information with unaffiliated third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, completing the transaction for your order.
Finally, the Company may in its sole discretion disclose personal information in special cases: (1) when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights of the Company or to anyone that could be harmed by such activities; (2) when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; (3) to any third party who may acquire the Company; and (4) in situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person.
We share your Personal Information with service providers to help us provide our services and fulfill our contracts with you, as described above. For example:
We use Shopify to power our online store. You can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.
We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
CCPA
If you are a resident of California, you have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you (also known as the ‘Right to Know’), to port it to a new service, and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or erased. If you would like to exercise these rights, contact us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com so we can help you.
If you would like to designate an authorized agent to submit these requests on your behalf, please contact us at the address below.
ENSURING YOUR SECURITY
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and ensures secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and thus protect all credit card ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information. Please note, however, that although we employ industry-standard security measures to safeguard the security of your personal information, no transmissions made on or through the Internet are guaranteed to be secure.
SAFE SHOPPING POLICY
Our policy is that you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping on our Website. It is determined that under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For example:
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en.You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
We share information about your use of the Site, your purchases, and your interaction with our ads on other websites with our advertising partners. We collect and share some of this information directly with our advertising partners, and in some cases through the use of cookies or other similar technologies (which you may consent to, depending on your location).
For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
[INCLUDE OPT-OUT LINKS FROM WHICHEVER SERVICES BEING USED. COMMON LINKS INCLUDE:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads]
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
TEXT/SMS MESSAGE CONSENT AND OPT-OUT
If you choose, you can provide your mobile phone number to receive text message alerts from our stores or sites to receive product and/or event information, tips or promotions. You agree that by providing your mobile phone number you expressly consent to receive automated marketing text messages from us to the mobile phone number provided. Consent is not required to purchase goods or services. Message and data rates will apply and you should check the rates of your mobile carrier. You can opt out from further text marketing communications by texting STOP to the SMS number used by MD Complete Skincare.
We may share your mobile phone number with service providers with whom we contract to assist us with the above activities, but we will not share your mobile phone number with third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. Text Messages are distributed via third party mobile network providers and, therefore, we cannot control certain factors relating to message delivery. Depending on the recipient's mobile carrier, it may not be possible to transmit the text message to the recipient successfully; nor is content available on all carriers. We do not claim or guarantee availability or performance of this service, including liability for transmission delays or message failures.
TECHNOLOGY UTILIZED
We employ several commonly used technologies on this Website: cookies, clear gifs, networking traffic monitoring and active scripting. We use these to monitor the performance of the Website, measure its effectiveness, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our Website and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns.
“Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent this. If you disable cookies, you may be unable to order or use other features of our Website. If you experience any problems, please email us at clientservice@mdcomplete.com
“Clear gifs" (also known as "web beacons" or “pixel tags”) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to help us better optimize our advertising.
“Network traffic monitoring" is programming that monitors and analyzes network traffic, and can be used to capture data being transmitted on a network, including plain-text data and computer IP addresses.
“Active scripting" is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Website, such as which links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or mobile device from our server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Website, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.
We may combine automatically collected Website usage information with your Personal Information. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information.
Cookies Necessary for the Functioning of the Store
Name
Function
_ab
Used in connection with access to admin.
_secure_session_id
Used in connection with navigation through a storefront.
cart
Used in connection with shopping cart.
cart_sig
Used in connection with checkout.
cart_ts
Used in connection with checkout.
checkout_token
Used in connection with checkout.
secret
Used in connection with checkout.
secure_customer_sig
Used in connection with customer login.
storefront_digest
Used in connection with customer login.
_shopify_u
Used to facilitate updating customer account information.
Reporting and Analytics
Name
Function
_tracking_consent
Tracking preferences.
_landing_page
Track landing pages
_orig_referrer
Track landing pages
_s
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_fs
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_s
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_sa_p
Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals.
_shopify_sa_t
Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals.
_shopify_y
Shopify analytics.
_y
Shopify analytics.
The length of time that a cookie remains on your computer or mobile device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies last until you stop browsing and persistent cookies last until they expire or are deleted. Most of the cookies we use are persistent and will expire between 30 minutes and two years from the date they are downloaded to your device.
You can control and manage cookies in various ways. Please keep in mind that removing or blocking cookies can negatively impact your user experience and parts of our website may no longer be fully accessible.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can choose whether or not to accept cookies through your browser controls, often found in your browser’s “Tools” or “Preferences” menu. For more information on how to modify your browser settings or how to block, manage or filter cookies can be found in your browser’s help file or through such sites as www.allaboutcookies.org.
Additionally, please note that blocking cookies may not completely prevent how we share information with third parties such as our advertising partners. To exercise your rights or opt-out of certain uses of your information by these parties, please follow the instructions in the “Behavioural Advertising” section above.
DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS
Some web browsers offer a "Do Not Track" ("DNT") signal. A DNT signal is a HTTP header field indicating your preference regarding tracking or cross-site user tracking. Although we are currently unable to honor DNT signals, we do not collect personal information when you visit our Website unless you provide such information to us. We also work with third parties that use tracking technologies on our Website in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and/or on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications, and use this information to determine which ads you see on third party Website and applications.
EXTERNAL LINKS
Our Website may offer links to and from other third party sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. For example, you may have linked to the MD Professional LLC brand site through a banner advertisement on another site. In such cases the site you have linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.
INTERNATIONAL USERS
Like almost every website, our Website may be accessed by an international audience. By visiting our Website and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and in jurisdictions which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes, both with regard to information we have previously collected from you and with regard to information we collect from you in the future. If you do not agree to the changes, please discontinue your use of our Website.
CONTACT
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at clientservice@mdcomplete.com or by mail using the details provided below:
MD Complete Skincare, 614 Wooster Pike Suite #1, Terrace Park, OH 45174
Last updated: 11/16/2020
Close (esc)
15% off your first purchase!
Join our mailing list to access promotions, new launches, and expert skincare tips.
Age verification
By clicking enter you are verifying that you are old enough to consume alcohol.
Your cart is currently empty.
Shop now
Powered By Discount Ninja
×
[[BODY]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1_LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2_LABEL]]
×
[[HEADER]]
[[MINIMIZED]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
×
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[TEXT]]
[[HEADER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[BODY]]
[[QUANTITY_LABEL]]
[[PRICE_LABEL]]
[[TIER_ROW]]
[[PRICE]]
[[LABEL]]
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ROW]]
